In my last video I fixed Amnesia Dark Descent
You guys wanna know why this game got destroyed by Call of Duty. First of all, it's set in Prussia. No one likes Prussia
That's why it doesn't exist anymore.
Since then every major publisher has contacted me and offered me employment
mostly as a joke
but some actually felt worried about the future and I get why. It is said that we will all switch over to mobile games by
This afternoon. So now it's up to me a youtuber with no experience in game development to save the entire industry
Wii U is probably the first thing to go
Because no one knows it exists or if they do they think it's a Wii Add-on
But I'm not blaming bad name choice or failure to build hype
I'm blaming Skyward Sword
The best Zeldas are always the dark Zeldas so thinking Nintendo
How dark can you go instead of having Link save Zelda from Ganondorf?
why not have him save her from a heroin addiction
and then fail
Saved Ubisoft Assassin's Creed unity was completely broken is hated by fans
Well everyone and the profit
millions
So you be just fire all your game testers if you have any. Saved. Konami is turning Silent Hill into pachinko machines
absolutely disgusting
Listen, Konami slot machines gotta appeal to the Western market saved Call of Duty
Ah Who am I kidding? You can't fix perfection saved sega
I love Total War and recently I've noticed that you've been very inspired by paradox games
Holy shit that's a lot DLC but in every paradox game you can play as a random Mongolian tribe
so I'm a need you to add a random Mongolian tribe in your next total war which is
Warhammer never heard of that historical period saved but that's not Sega's crown jewel
*Sonic racing theme*
Jewel is a strong word when we see some sonic fan content. We think to ourselves
Oh, I guess God just gave up. So I wanted to add that feeling to the games then
I find out you already did that
Twice but the series holds up when you think Final Fantasies exclusive buyers
What do you think of Surgeons? Then
You're probably a Final Fantasy buyer you weeaboo weebs square are great for business
Because they never tell you if something is terrible like Final Fantasy 13
But you know the old saying there's no such thing as a bad video game just bad marketing
There was another company that had your exact problems where only weeaboos would buy their products and that company was
Marlboro back in the 50s so they thought what's the opposite of a weeaboo a cowboy so square I have made a commercial
Just for you
after a hard day of doing cowboy stuff like
riding horses and
milking
Horses, I like to relax with some good old Final Fantasy 15 the classic taste safe
Realizing now that doing every franchise is a waste of time. Let's try to fix everything at once
The three undisputed greatest games of all time are completely different. Let's analyze them to find similarities
First thought they are all shooter games
No
Halo one is more of an emotional journey. Oh, they're all sci-fi games
No, the first levels of Halo 2 takes place on earth
The only thing I can think of is that by today's standards all three have pretty awful graphics
All games in Metacritic top lists have pretty awful graphics
But the point of this video wasn't to improve quality of video games. It was to make more money
How do other industries do it? I've been researching this for the past month
And I finally found a solution that can not only save the game companies millions
But also mature the industry guys
We need child labor